Preliminary Guide to the Federation for American Immigration Reform (FAIR) records, 1867-2006 MS2195
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject files, 1974-2006; Series 8
  - Organizations, 1990-2003; Series 8 Subseries 8
    - NCPA - National Center for Policy, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - NEA, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - NGR Forum, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 233, Folder 10)
    - NHA, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 233, Folder 7)
    - NPG, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 233, Folder 9)
    - Negative Population Growth, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 255, Folder 9)
    - Organizations: O, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - Organizations: P, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - PEB, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Pioneer Fund, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - Population Crisis Commission, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 234, Folder 5)
    - Population Institute, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - PRB (Population Reference Bureau) [1/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 234, Folder 7)
    - PRB (Population Reference Bureau) [2/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 234, Folder 8)
    - PRB (Population Reference Bureau) [3/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - Population Resource Center, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - Progressive Policy Institute (PPI), undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - Project USA's, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - Organizations: Q, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 235, Folder 5)
    - Organizations: R, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - Rand [1/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 235, Folder 7)
    - Rand [2/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Rand [3/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - READ, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 236, Folder 4)
    - Organzations: S, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 236, Folder 5)
    - Sierra Club [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 237, Folder 1)
    - Sierra Club [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 237, Folder 2)
    - Social Contract [1/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 237, Folder 3)
    - Social Contract [2/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 237, Folder 4)
    - Social Contract [3/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 237, Folder 5)
    - Southern Poverty Law Center, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 238, Folder 1)
    - Organizations: T, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 238, Folder 2)
    - Trilateral Commission, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - Organizations: U, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - UN Fund for Population Activity, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 238, Folder 5)
    - UN High Commission on Refugees [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 238, Folder 6)
    - UN High Commission on Refugees [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 238, Folder 7)
    - Urban Institute [1/5], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 238, Folder 8)
    - Urban Institute [2/5], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 238, Folder 9)
    - Urban Institute [3/5], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 239, Folder 1)
    - Urban Institute [4/5], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 239, Folder 2)
    - Urban Institute [5/5], undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 239, Folder 3)
    - US Committee for Refugees, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 239, Folder 5)
    - US English, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 239, Folder 4)
    - USWA, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 239, Folder 6)
    - Organizations: V, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 239, Folder 7)
    - Voices of Citizens Together, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 239, Folder 8)
    - Organizations: W, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 239, Folder 9)
    - World and I, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 239, Folder 11)
    - World Bank, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 239, Folder 10)
    - XYZ: Zero Population Growth, undated; Series 8 Subseries 8 (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - Countries, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9
    Arranged alphabetically by country name.
    This subseries contains subject files maintained by FAIR related to the topic of immigration organized by country.
    - Africa, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - Albania, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - Argentina, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 224, Folder 16)
    - Asia, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 11)
    - Australia, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 227, Folder 7)
    - Austria, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 2)
    - Bahamas, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - Bangledesh, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 12)
    - Belgium, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - Bosnia, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 4)
    - Burma, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 13)
    - Cambodia, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 14)
    - Canada, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 220, Folder 11)
    - Caribbean, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - Central America, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - Chile, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 224, Folder 17)
    - China, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 15)
    - Columbia, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 224, Folder 18)
    - Countries/Continents, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 220, Folder 9)
    - Cuba, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 220, Folder 8)
    - Cyprus, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 5)
    - Czech Republic, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 6)
    - Denmark, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 7)
    - Dominican Republic, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 224, Folder 10)
    - El Salvador, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - England, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 8)
    - Estonia, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 10)
    - European Union, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 224, Folder 21)
    - Finland, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 9)
    - France, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 11)
    - Germany, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 12)
    - Greece, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 13)
    - Guam, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 224, Folder 13)
    - Guatemala, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - Haiti, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 224, Folder 11)
    - Hong Kong, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 16)
    - India, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 17)
    - Indonesia, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 18)
    - Iran, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 227, Folder 2)
    - Iraq, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - Ireland, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 14)
    - Israel, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - Italy, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 15)
    - Jamaica, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 224, Folder 14)
    - Japan, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 19)
    - Kenya, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 5)
    - Latvia, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 16)
    - Laos, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 20)
    - Malaysia, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 21)
    - Marianas Islands, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 219, Folder 15)
    - Mexico [1/2]., undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 220, Folder 12)
    - Mexico [2/2]., undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - Middle East, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - Montserrat, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 224, Folder 12)
    - Netherlands, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 17)
    - New Zealand, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 227, Folder 8)
    - Nicaragua, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - Nigeria, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 6)
    - North America, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 220, Folder 10)
    - Norway, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 18)
    - Palestine, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 227, Folder 5)
    - Peru, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 224, Folder 19)
    - Philippines, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 22)
    - Poland, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 19)
    - public assistance, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - Puerto Rico, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 219, Folder 14)
    - Romania, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 20)
    - Russia, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 225, Folder 21)
    - Rwanda, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 7)
    - Saudi Arabia, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 227, Folder 6)
    - Somalia, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 8)
    - South America, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 224, Folder 15)
    - South Korea, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 23)
    - Spain, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - Sudan, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 10)
    - Sweden, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - Switzerland, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - Taiwan, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 24)
    - Thailand, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 25)
    - Tibet, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 26)
    - United States., undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Territories, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 219, Folder 13)
    - Venezuala, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 224, Folder 20)
    - Vietnam, undated; Series 8 Subseries 9 (Box 226, Folder 27)
  - Fair publications, undated; Series 8 Subseries 10
    This subseries contains subject files maintained by FAIR with various FAIR publications.
    Arranged in no particular order.
    - Meeting of the Board of Directors: Mailbag Clips, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 253, Folder 1)
    - FAIR Report to the Executive Director, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 253, Folder 2)
    - Reference [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 253, Folder 3)
    - Reference [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 253, Folder 4)
    - Hand-outs [FAIR Immigration Primer for Students]., undated; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 253, Folder 5)
    - FAIR Research Updates, 1994-2002; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 253, Folder 6)
    - Memos [of FAIR], 1992-2001; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 253, Folder 7)
    - [FAIR Emails, newspaper articles, publications, handwritten notes]., undated; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 253, Folder 8)
    - [FAIR Publications on Foreign Workers], undated; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 252, Folder 1)
    - [FAIR Publications on Population and Environment], undated; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 252, Folder 2)
    - [FAIR Publications on Schools and Education], undated; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 252, Folder 3)
    - How to Win the Immigration Debate, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 252, Folder 4)
    - Ten Steps to Ending Illegal Immigration, 1995; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 252, Folder 5)
    - The Immigration Handbook, 1995; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 252, Folder 6)
    - You Can Help Reform Immigration, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 252, Folder 7)
    - [Ten Years of FAIR and Misc.], undated; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 252, Folder 8)
    - [FAIR Library Selection and Filing Methods], undated; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 252, Folder 9)
    - FAIR Annual Reports, 2001-2002; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 251, Folder 1)
    - FAIR Population Projections, 2006; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 251, Folder 2)
    - FAIR Publications on the Economy, undated; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 251, Folder 3)
    - FAIR Publications on Policy and Laws, undated; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 251, Folder 4)
    - FAIR Publications on Terrorism and Immigration, undated; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 251, Folder 5)
    - Immigration 2000: The Century of the New American Sweatshop, undated; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 251, Folder 6)
    - FAIR Publications on Health and Families, undated; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 251, Folder 7)
    - FAIR: Organization Information/Mission Packet, undated; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 251, Folder 8)
    - Various FAIR Publications, undated; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 251, Folder 9)
    - FAIR Immigration Report, 1993 May - 1995 December; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 250, Folder 1)
    - FAIR Immigration Report, 1996 January - 1998 April; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 250, Folder 2)
    - FAIR Immigration Report, 1998 May - 2000 March; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 250, Folder 3)
    - FAIR Immigration Report, 2000 April -2002 April; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 250, Folder 4)
    - FAIR Immigration Report, 1979 October - 1985 January; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 249, Folder 1)
    - FAIR Immigration Report, 1985 February - 1989 June; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 249, Folder 2)
    - FAIR Immigration Report, 1989 June - April 1993; Series 8 Subseries 10 (Box 249, Folder 3)
  - Publications, undated; Series 8 Subseries 11
    This subseries contains publications related to immigration. These publications were collected by FAIR.
    - [Public Policy Institute of California Publications I], undated; Series 8 Subseries 11 (Box 254, Folder 1)
    - [Public Policy Institute of California Publications II], undated; Series 8 Subseries 11 (Box 254, Folder 2)
    - CAPS: Californians for Population Stabalization Newsletters, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 11 (Box 254, Folder 3)
    - CAPS: Californians for Population Stabalization Newsletters, 2005; Series 8 Subseries 11 (Box 255, Folder 4)
    - Carrying Capacity Network Bulletin, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 11 (Box 254, Folder 4)
    - The Non-Profit Agenda, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 11 (Box 254, Folder 5)
    - Hispanic Link Weekly Report, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 11 (Box 254, Folder 6)
    - Population Bulletin, 1999-2005; Series 8 Subseries 11 (Box 254, Folder 7)
    - Population Press, 2002; Series 8 Subseries 11 (Box 254, Folder 8)
    - CCIS Mexico Project, 2001-2005; Series 8 Subseries 11 (Box 254, Folder 10)
    - [Admissions Decisions], 1994; Series 8 Subseries 11 (Box 254, Folder 11)
    - Breach of Faith: American Churches and the Immigration Crisis, 2004; Series 8 Subseries 11 (Box 256, Folder 8)
    - [Review Copy of "The Population Fix" by Ed Hartman], 2004; Series 8 Subseries 11 (Box 256, Folder 9)
    - [GAO Immigration Benefit Fraud], 2002; Series 8 Subseries 11 (Box 256, Folder 10)
    - The Social Contract: Common Sense on Mass Immigration, 2004; Series 8 Subseries 11 (Box 254, Folder 12)
  - Center for Immigration Studies, 1996-2006; Series 8 Subseries 12
    This subseries contains subject files maintained by FAIR related to the organization the Center for Immigration Studies. There are also files for this organization in subseries 8.
    - Backgrounder [Center for Immigration Studies Publication], 2004-2005; Series 8 Subseries 12 (Box 248, Folder 1)
    - Backgrounder [Center for Immigration Studies Publication], 1996-2006; Series 8 Subseries 12 (Box 248, Folder 2)
    - Immigration and Nationality Policies of Leading Migration Nations, 1992; Series 8 Subseries 12 (Box 248, Folder 3)
    - Center for Immigration Studies Publications, undated; Series 8 Subseries 12 (Box 248, Folder 4)
    - Center for Immigration Studies Publications, undated; Series 8 Subseries 12 (Box 248, Folder 5)
    - Center for Immigration Studies, undated; Series 8 Subseries 12 (Box 248, Folder 6)
    - Center for Immigration Studies, undated; Series 8 Subseries 12 (Box 255, Folder 11)